wativ.com 2016-12-04

# Privacy Policy • Wativ.com

Wativ.com privacy policy is designed to provide our visitors quality coupons and deals while keeping trust in dealing with our clients and partners. In this policy we will inform you how we collect, use, and protect your personal information and help you making up to date decisions about using coupons and deals at Wativ.com.

## What Information do we collect?

Your privacy is essential to us and you may use wativ.com anonymously but you are welcome to provide your personal information i.e. email address for our coupon newsletter that will be used to provide you with the latest deals and offers from our partner merchants. We assure that your email information will never be sold or distributed. At any time users who no longer wish to receive our newsletter may always opt out by following the unsubscribe link at the bottom of wativ.com newsletter.

## Using Cookies

Wativ.com also uses “cookies” and web server logs to collect information about how our site is used by our visitors. Cookies are a feature of your web browser that contains bits of information that help personalize your web experience. You may always opt out of cookie collection by turning them off in your internet browsers settings. Cookies and web logs may track the time of visit, time spent at our site, which pages were viewed, and the sites visited just before and just after our site. This information does not contain any personal information about you and is collected on an aggregate basis.

## External Links

Our site contains links to other merchant websites. We are not responsible for the practices, policies, or content of such sites and encourage our users to review the individual policies therein.

## Change in Policy Notification

We can change any portion of our policy in the ongoing development of our website and we will update this page for any change in our policy. Under the circumstance that any change is made to the collection or distribution of personal information, we will notify you via email. However, we will use any information you provide (namely your email) under the privacy policy under which it was collected.  
If you have any question or query regarding this privacy policy, you are welcome to [contact us](http://wativ.com/contact-us/).
